Drew Bradford

Middletown New Jersey, 07748 United States
917.373.3131 <u>drewbradfordxyz@gmail.com</u> <u>www.drewbradford.xyz</u>

Profile

I'm a JavaScript and QuickBase developer with a tech and insurance background. I create tools to configure and scope services, increase user productivity, reduce business complexity, improve risk management, streamline workflows and provide data insights.

Projects

A UI tool built with JavaScript and QuickBase to define and scope services. Subject matter experts import data into QuickBase tables to generate the content and behavior of the custom UI. Users of that UI scope services by assigning task quantities, add co-provider information, additional custom roles and expenses.

Word Document generation tool for legal agreements spanning the globe. Users have full UI access to edit the document templates. Many factors determine which type of document is generated, which sections are used, the verbiage, as well as the formatting of the document.

A bid generation tool that does a multi stage cost factor analysis to determine the cost of multiple services and combine them into a bid with milestones attached.

A risk category matrix to assign, measure and flag risky bids for evaluation to prevent financial loss.

Skills

QuickBase, Javascript, React, Vue, NodeJS, Figma, Jira, Agile Development, REST API, Relational Database, Pipelines, Formula Fields, Forms, Reports

Employment

Hitachi Vantara - JavaScript QuickBase Developer

June 2020 - May 2024, Remote

CTC Transportation Insurance - QuickBase JavaScript Developer

June 2016 - August 2017, New Jersey

Education

Pratt Institute,

Bachelors Digital Art - Brooklyn, NY 2009-2013